A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Japanese Studies and Korean Studies, Record Group 3, Series 7 FA1775
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) program files, 1946-1995; 1; 14.15 Cubic Feet 36.75 document boxes: 34.75 letter size boxes and 2 legal size boxes
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Proposals, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 128)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Fall 1990 Meeting, Boston, Massachusetts (Box 10, Folder 129)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Spring 1990 Meeting, Chicago, Illinois, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 130)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Fall 1989 Meeting, New York City, New York (Box 10, Folder 131)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Fall 1990 Meeting, Boston, Massachusetts (Box 10, Folder 132)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) general correspondence, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 133)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) correspondence - Blair Ruble and Monique Carroll, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 134)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Fall 1993 Meeting, New York City, New York - Agenda items, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 135-136)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Spring 1992 Meeting, Washington D.C. - Agenda items, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 137-138)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) and East Asia Regional Research Working Group (EARRWG) - Meeting agenda items, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 139)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Spring 1993 Meeting, Los Angeles, California - Agenda items, 1989-1993 (Box 12, Folder 140-141)
  - Health, Illness, and Medical Care in Japan, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 142)
  - Democratizing Japan, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 143)
  - Local Institutions in National Development conference papers, 1980-1988 (Box 12, Folder 144)
  - The Yatoi symposium - Ardath Burks, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 145)
  - Technology Innovation and Diffusion in Japan, Robert Cole and Gary Saxonhouse - Conference papers publication, 1977-1988 (Box 12, Folder 146)
  - Technology Innovation and Diffusion in Japan, Robert Cole and Gary Saxonhouse, 1975-1987 (Box 12, Folder 147-148)
  - Japan-United States relations, Chihiro Hosoya and Akira Iriye - Japan, the U.S., and the World conference, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 149)
  - Japan-United States relations, Chihiro Hosoya and Akira Iriye, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 150)
  - Japan-United States relations, Chihiro Hosoya and Akira Iriye, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 151)
  - Japan-United States relations, Chihiro Hosoya and Akira Iriye - Ted Bestor correspondence, 1984 June (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Japan-United States relations, Chihiro Hosoya and Akira Iriye - Japan, the U.S., and the World conference, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 153)
  - Japan-United States relations, Chihiro Hosoya and Akira Iriye - Conference papers publication, 1983-1989 (Box 13, Folder 154)
  - Japan-United States relations, Chihiro Hosoya and Akira Iriye, 1983-1988 (Box 13, Folder 155)
  - Workshop on Enterprise Groups in Japan, W. Mark Fruin, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 156)
  - Gender issues in Japan, 1978-1985 (Box 13, Folder 157-158)
  - Gender issues in Japan, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 159)
  - Gender issues in Japan, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 160)
  - Beyond Insularity: Social and Ethical Analyses of Japanese Values in a World Context, William LaFleur, 1985 September (Box 13, Folder 161)
  - Emotional development in Japan conference, Joseph Campos and Kazuo Miyake, 1984-1986 (Box 13, Folder 162)
  - Japanese imperialism in China - Conference papers publication, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 163)
  - Japanese imperialism in China, 1979-1988 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Japan prewar business history, William Wray, 1982-1989 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Japan prewar business history, William Wray, 1981-1988 (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - Cognition and the arts in Japan, Michael Cole and Yutaka Sayeki, 1983-1986 (Box 14, Folder 167)
  - Nobi Regional Project, William Skinner, 1983-1988 (Box 14, Folder 168)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) - Miscellaneous cross-national collaborative research and conferences, 1976-1986 (Box 15, Folder 169-170)
  - The American Occupation, Robert Ward and Yoshikazu Sakamoto, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) - Cultural criticism and philosophy conference papers, 1977-1984 (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - Social Stratification and Mobility in Japan and the United States, Donald Treiman and Ken'ichi Tominaga - Conference papers publication, 1978-1986 (Box 15, Folder 173-175)
  - Socialization in Early Childhood in Japan and the United States, 1978-1983 (Box 16, Folder 176-177)
  - Child Development in Japan and the United States, Harold Stevenson, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 178)
  - Local opposition and local politics in Japan, Terry MacDougall, 1980-1987 (Box 16, Folder 179-180)
  - Gender in Japan, Mary Brinton, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Gender in Japan, Mary Brinton, 1985-1987 (Box 17, Folder 182-183)
  - Communication technology in Japan, the United States, and Western Europe, David Weaver, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 184)
  - Children's concepts of life in Japan and the U.S., Giyoo Hatano and Robert Siegler, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 185)
  - Capital Cities in Japan and Europe in the Early Modern Period, James McClain, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 186)
  - Media and Politics in Japan, Hiroshi Akuto and Susan Pharr, 1978-1988 (Box 17, Folder 187-188)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) - Miscellaneous research and conference proposals, 1973-1983 (Box 18, Folder 189-190)
  - Media and Politics in Japan, Hiroshi Akuto and Susan Pharr, 1981-1986 (Box 18, Folder 191-192)
  - One Party Dominance Project, T.J. Pempel and Michio Muramatsu - Conference papers publication, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 193)
  - One Party Dominance Project, T.J. Pempel and Michio Muramatsu, 1981-1989 (Box 18, Folder 194)
  - One Party Dominance Project, T.J. Pempel and Michio Muramatsu, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 195)
  - One Party Dominance Project, T.J. Pempel and Michio Muramatsu, 1981-1984 (Box 18, Folder 196)
  - Media and Politics in Japan, Hiroshi Akuto and Susan Pharr, 1975-1988 (Box 19, Folder 197-198)
  - Postmodernity in Japan, J. Victor Koschmann and Naoki Sakai, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 199)
  - Postmodernity in Japan, J. Victor Koschmann and Naoki Sakai, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 200)
  - Asian Studies Newsletter Archives bibliography, Frank Joseph Shulman, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 201)
  - Cultural Criticism in Interwar Japan, Thomas Rimer, 1965-1989 (Box 19, Folder 202-204)
  - Social Control in Early Childhood Education, Thomas Rohlen and Catherine Lewis, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 205)
  - Social Control in Early Childhood Education, Thomas Rohlen and Catherine Lewis, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 206)
  - Social Control in Early Childhood Education, Thomas Rohlen and Catherine Lewis, 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 207)
  - Public and private interests in Japan, Gary Allinson, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 208)
  - Public and private interests in Japan, Gary Allinson, 1987-1989 (Box 20, Folder 209-210)
  - Joint Advisory Committee on International Programs (JACIP) report - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS), 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 211)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC), 1988 (Box 20, Folder 212)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Western New York and Southern Ontario, circa 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 213)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminal Program - Midwest, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 214)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Rocky Mountain and Southwest, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 215)
  - Dissent and control in the East and West, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 216)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Washington and Southeast, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 217)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Midwest, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 218)
  - Japan Foundation - Traveling Japan Seminar and Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 219)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - New England, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 220)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Washington and Southeast, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 221)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Triangle East Asia Colloquium (TEAC), 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 222)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Southern, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 223)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Triangle East Asian Colloquium (TEAC), 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 224)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Washington and Southeast, 1987-1989 (Box 21, Folder 225)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Southern, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 226)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 227)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program, 1986-1989 (Box 21, Folder 228)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program, 1987-1989 (Box 22, Folder 229)
  - Japan Foundation University Consortia Survey - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) application, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 230)
  - Japan Foundation University Consortia Survey, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 231)
  - Japan Foundation University Consortia Survey, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 232)
  - International History of East Asia, 1550-1750, 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 233)
  - International History of East Asia, 1550-1750, 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 234)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) - Miscellaneous meeting minutes and reports, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 235)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - New England, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 236)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program papers and other documents, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 237-238)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 239)
  - SSRC Indochina Studies Program (ISP) updates, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 240-241)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC) Grant No. 79-12, 1978-1980 (Box 23, Folder 242)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC) Grant No. 80E, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 243)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) write-ups for SSRC Items, 1968-1979 (Box 23, Folder 244)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) write-ups for SSRC Items - Catherine Lewis article, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 245)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) budget, 1978-1982 (Box 23, Folder 246)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) membership - CV's, 1984-1987 (Box 23, Folder 247)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) membership - CV's, 1984-1987 (Box 23, Folder 248)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) 1979 grant awards (Box 24, Folder 249)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) 1978 grant awards (Box 24, Folder 250)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) 1977 grant awards (Box 24, Folder 251)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) 1976 grant awards (Box 24, Folder 252)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) 1975 grant awards (Box 24, Folder 253)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) 1974 grant awards (Box 24, Folder 254)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) 1973 grant awards, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 255)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) 1972 grant awards (Box 24, Folder 256)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) 1981-1982 grants - Finances, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 257)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) general file, 1983-1986 (Box 24, Folder 258)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) general file - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 259)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) general file - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 260)
  - SSRC general file - Fundamental forms templates, 1981-1987 (Box 24, Folder 261)
  - SSRC general file - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) and Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) mailing lists, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 262)
  - SSRC general file - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) and Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) mailing lists, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 263)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) 1980-1981 grant awards (Box 24, Folder 264)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Spring 1980 Meeting (Box 24, Folder 265)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Fall 1980 Meeting, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 266)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) annual reports segments, 1970-1983 (Box 24, Folder 267)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Fall 1982 Meeting (Box 25, Folder 268)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Spring 1982 Meeting, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 269)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Fall 1981 Meeting, 1979-1982 (Box 25, Folder 270)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Spring 1981 Meeting, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 271)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) 1982-1983 committee membership (Box 25, Folder 272)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) - 1982 Joint Committees Assembly (Box 25, Folder 273)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) grant applications - Committee review assignments, undated (Box 25, Folder 274)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Fall 1985 Meeting (Box 25, Folder 275)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Spring 1985 Meeting, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 276)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Spring 1984 Meeting, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 277)
  - European Association for Japanese Studies (EAJS), 1973-1982 (Box 25, Folder 278)
  - Intellectual refugees - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 279)
  - Intellectual refugees - SSRC intellectual refugee letter, 1976-1984 (Box 26, Folder 280)
  - Intellectual refugees - SSRC intellectual refugee letter responses, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 281)
  - Intellectual refugees, 1980-1984 (Box 26, Folder 282-283)
  - International House of Japan Japanese Social Scientist Fellowship Program - Ford Foundation, Carl Green, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 284)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC) grant application, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 285)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC) grant support, 1987-1989 (Box 26, Folder 286)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC) general correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 26, Folder 287)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC) grant for Advanced Research Grant 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 288)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC) Grant No. 84-102 Cultural Criticism in Interwar Japan, 1986-1988 (Box 26, Folder 289)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC) Grant No. 85-35, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 290)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC) Grant No. 83-04 Cultural Criticism in Interwar Japan, 1980-1986 (Box 26, Folder 291)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) correspondence - Ted Bestor to Patricia Steinhoff, 1983 December 20 (Box 27, Folder 292)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC) Grant No. 80-74 Advanced Research Grant 1980-1981, 1980-1984 (Box 27, Folder 293)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC) Grant No. 81-24 Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Research Project Planning, 1980-1983 (Box 27, Folder 294)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC) Grant No. 81-78 Advanced Research Grant 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 295)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC) Grant No. 81-41 Japanese aesthetics, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 296)
  - 1988 Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) and Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) correspondence (Box 27, Folder 297-298)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Research Planning Grant 1988-1989 declinations (Box 27, Folder 299)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC) Grant No. 88-86 Advanced Research Grant 1988-1989 - Grant agreement (Box 27, Folder 300)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission (JUSFC) proposal - Media and politics in Japan, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 301)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Japan Foundation grant proposal 1986-1987, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 302)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 303)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program 1986-1987, 1983-1987 (Box 27, Folder 304)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 305)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program 1986-1987, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 306)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Florida 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 307)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Florida 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 308)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Rocky Mountain and Southwest 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 309)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Triangle East Asia Colloquium (TEAC) 1986-1987, 1985-1987 (Box 28, Folder 310)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Washington and Southeast 1986-1987, 1985-1987 (Box 28, Folder 311)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Washington and Southeast 1986-1987 Japan Constitution commemoration, 1946-1987 (Box 28, Folder 312)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Western New York and Southern Ontario 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 313)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 314)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Triangle East Asia Colloquium (TEAC), 1979-1985 (Box 28, Folder 315-316)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Florida, 1981-1986 (Box 28, Folder 317)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Western New York and Southern Ontario, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 318)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - General, 1984-1985 (Box 28, Folder 319)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Washington and Southeast, 1976-1985 (Box 28, Folder 320)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Midwest 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 321)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - General, 1971-1985 (Box 29, Folder 322)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Midwest, 1975-1985 (Box 29, Folder 323-325)
  - Tokugawa to Meiji period transition, Marius Jansen and Gilbert Rozman, 1977-1982 (Box 29, Folder 326)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - Rocky Mountain and Southwest, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 327)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Regional Seminar Program - General, 1974-1985 (Box 29, Folder 328-329)
  - Japan-United States Friendship Commission(JUSFC) grant proposals, 1981-1985 (Box 30, Folder 330)
  - Japan Society for the Promotion of Science (JSPS) and Science Council of Japan (SCJ) reports, 1975-1984 (Box 30, Folder 331-332)
  - Japan Society for the Promotion of Science (JSPS), 1981-1983 (Box 30, Folder 333)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS)-Japan Society for the Promotion of Science (JSPS) collaborative research projects, 1980-1983 (Box 30, Folder 334)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS)-Japan Society for the Promotion of Science (JSPS) collaborative research projects - Author responses, 1977-1983 (Box 30, Folder 335)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS)-Japan Society for the Promotion of Science (JSPS) collaborative research projects - History report, 1972-1983 (Box 31, Folder 336)
  - Ford Foundation and National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) 1980 proposals, 1972-1984 (Box 31, Folder 337)
  - Japan Society for the Promotion of Science (JSPS) application forms, undated (Box 31, Folder 338)
  - Japan Institute of International Affairs (JIIA) - White Papers of Japan 1984-1985, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 339)
  - United States Department of Education - Japanese Education Today, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 340)
  - Japanese Studies Field Survey - List of individuals, circa 1983 (Box 31, Folder 341)
  - United States-Japan Conference on Cultural and Educational Interchange (CULCON) 1978 Symposium (Box 31, Folder 342)
  - International House of Japan - List of Nitobe Fellows, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 343)
  - Japanese Studies Field Survey - List of institutions, 1983 May (Box 31, Folder 344)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Fall 1987 Meeting - Agenda (Box 32, Folder 345-346)
  - Japanese Studies Field Survey - List of individuals, circa 1983 (Box 32, Folder 347)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Spring 1988 Meeting - Agenda, 1986-1988 (Box 32, Folder 348)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Fall 1988 Meeting - Agenda (Box 32, Folder 349-350)
  - Ford Foundation - Refugees and Migrants: Problems and Program Responses, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 351)
  - The Japan Institute of International Affairs (JIIA) - White Papers of Japan 1983-1984, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 352)
  - The International House of Japan Annual Report 32 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 353)
  - The Fukuoka UNESCO Association - Overseas Japanese Studies Institutions, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 354)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange (JCIE) - Research Institutions in Japan, 1973 January (Box 33, Folder 355)
  - The International House of Japan Annual Report 31 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 356)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange (JCIE) Program Report 1985-1986, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 357)
  - Miscellaneous reports, circa 1985 (Box 33, Folder 358)
  - United States-Japan Conference on Cultural and Educational Exchange (CULCON) Joint Committee Meeting, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 359)
  - United States-Japan Conference on Cultural and Educational Exchange (CULCON) IX, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 360-361)
  - United States-Japan Conference on Cultural and Educational Exchange (CULCON) XI, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 362)
  - United States-Japan Conference on Cultural and Educational Exchange (CULCON) XI, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 363)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) and Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) budget, 1982-1986 (Box 34, Folder 364-365)
  - Postwar Japan as History, Andrew Gordon and John Dower, 1985-1989 (Box 34, Folder 366-367)
  - International History of East Asia, William Atwell and Ronald Toby, 1984-1990 (Box 35, Folder 368-369)
  - Japanese syntax, Susumu Kuno and Masayoshi Shibatani, 1986-1989 (Box 35, Folder 370)
  - Attachment and Support over the Life Span, Toni Antonucci, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 371)
  - Life cycle development, Nancy Shand, 1986-1988 (Box 35, Folder 372)
  - Narrating Japan, James Fujii, Edward Fowler, and Richard Okada, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 373)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) general file, 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 374)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Spring 1987 Meeting, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 375)
  - Joint Committee on Japanese Studies (JCJS) Fall 1986 Meeting, 1976-1986 (Box 35, Folder 376)